Nano Banana Pro lets you turn this into
this [music] with nothing but your phone
camera. Nano Banana Pro is Google's new
AI image generation model and it just
came out. And this is the first AI ever
that lets you make a full Amazon listing
image set with no photographer, no
graphic designer whatsoever. And for the
first time in history, large brands and
aggregators have started trusting this
AI model instead of photographers and
designers to create high converting
images for [music] their top selling
products on Amazon. In this video, I'm
going to show you exactly how to use
Nano Banana Pro to create a set of high
converting Amazon listing images like
[music] these for your Amazon products
by yourself at home with nothing but
your phone. And bear with me, guys. I
got a little sick at [music]
Friendsgiving, so I might be taking
breaks to blow my nose here. Later on in
the video, I'm also going to give you
the ultimate guide to Nano Banana Pro
for Amazon sellers, which is the best
guide on the internet, showing you how
to use Nano Banana Pro to develop a full
professional set of Amazon listing
images [music] that are high converting.
And it's going to go through some of the
same examples that we go through in
[music] this video. So, if you want that
guide, I'll show you how to get it later
on in this video, and I'll link to it in
the description of this video. So, stick
around to get that. Okay. So, your first
step is to download the Gemini app on
your phone. I'm going to put links to
the Gemini app. This is the Google's AI.
It's called Gemini. And Nano Banana Pro
is the image generation model inside
Gemini, Google's AI app. So, you can
download that on your phone either if
you have an iPhone or an Android. I put
the links in the description of this
video to download. Now, this whole thing
I'm going to be doing with a phone. And
the reason I do it with a phone is very
simple that the phone has camera on it.
And [music]
using the image generation app, you're
going to be taking pictures since what
you're doing is doing images of a
product that you have in your physical
space, you need to be able to constantly
take new pictures and new angles and
close-ups of it to give the model more
context. So, you want to be doing all
this on your phone, not on your desktop.
So, once you download the app, you're
going to open it up, and what you're
going to do is go down here where it
says fast and switch it to thinking with
3 Pro. And then you'll see a little
circle that says thinking there. Now
you're on Nanobanana Pro, which is the
most powerful AI image generation model
for product images in particular in the
world right now. Okay. So, we're going
to do this interactively. So, I want you
to follow along with me in this video.
While you're watching this video, or at
least directly after watching this
video, I want you to do the same thing
and just test it out for yourself
because that's how you're going to
actually learn. So, what I'm going to do
is take a product here on my desk, take
a picture of it, and turn it into a
primary Amazon listing image, which is
the first image you see in search
results. So, I chose this product. This
is a bike pump. It's an electric bike
pump. The key is you need to give
usually multiple angles and multiple
photos of the product to give the AI
enough context and reference to know the
full shape and features of the product.
In this case, I fed the AI three images.
And here's the three images that I used.
I tried to get enough context to show
the model, the engravings on the
buttons, the display, the charge ports
on the back, and the full size and scale
of the product. And by the way, it
really helps if you have a sense of
scale. You want to show the product in
your hand or next to something else that
has very obvious scale. And that can be
money or a laptop or a phone or
something that gives the AI a sense of
scale. If you just show the product by
itself, like against a wall or on the
floor, it's really hard for the AI to
tell how big it is. So, you want to give
it enough context to show it a sense of
scale. So, I gave it these three images,
and here's what I got as a result. Now,
I had to go back and forth a little bit
to get this, but this is actually pretty
good. It got the text right. It's called
[music]
Psych Plus. It got the It got the
display right. It got the hose. It got
the nozzle on the hose and even like the
[music] details like the little
engravings on the nozzle. It got a lot
of stuff right in this image. Now, I
could refine this even further, and it
did take me a little bit of back and
forth to get this, [music]
but what I'm going to do in this video
is walk you through a full example of us
creating from soup to nuts a full Amazon
product listing image set. And we're
going to do that together. I'm going to
show you all of the issues I run into
and how I overcame those issues so
[music] that when you run into
roadblocks using Nano Banana Pro for
your Amazon listings, you can figure out
how to overcome those roadblocks
yourself. And there is a trick to it.
[music] So, I'm going to show you what
those tricks are now. But this quick
example at the beginning here of turning
these three images into [music] this
primary image should show you and give
you some sense of how powerful this AI
image generation model is. Now, if we
wanted to do this in the past before
this model, we would have had to hire a
3D rendering artist to make this [music]
happen. Now, you can do it for free with
an app on your phone and just using your
phone camera at home if you have the
product physically in your space. It's
pretty incredible. So, let's do this
together. First, we're going to take
some pictures. And I chose to use this
product, which is a diffuser. But you
can choose to work on your product if
you have it in front of you. Or you can
just pick up a product around your
office or your house to ride along with
me while we do this. And we're going to
do this together. Ready? So, I started
out with these four products that I took
by myself with the product in my hand
with my phone. And you'll notice that I
got different zoom distances and
different angles. And in particular, I
made sure to get close-ups of the parts
that needed specific fine detail. Like
in this case, there's an engraving on
each of the small buttons on the
diffuser. I wanted to make sure that the
model understood those engravings and
could see them clearly so that it could
render them properly. Okay, now we're
going to open the Gemini app. Make sure
that it's in thinking mode first, which
is the Pro version. That's how you get
Nano Banana Pro. And then we're going to
upload these four images by hitting the
plus in the lower left side of the
screen and just selecting these four
images. Then we're going to add in the
prompt that you see here. Create a clean
product photo rendering of this product
to be used as the primary image on an
Amazon listing. This is a good first
level prompt. And here's the first tip
that I'm going to share with you guys is
that with Nano Banana Pro, you don't
have to go so crazy with your prompt
engineering. You don't have to have
another AI generate like a page long
prompt for you. This model is meant to
understand human language. So you don't
have to have an insane prompt where
you're specifying the make and model of
the camera used to take the photo and
stuff like that. You really don't need
to go that crazy. So those are the
images that we uploaded and that's the
prompt we uploaded. And here is the
result. Now this came out really good.
Actually, you're not always going to get
it on the first try. In my case, I did.
It's if you zoom in on this image, you
can see the grain of the ceramic. You
could see the engravings on the buttons.
You can see a little mist coming out of
the top. The model pretty much got it
dead on. Now, this isn't always going to
happen, and I'm going to show you later
on when we're generating the other
images how the model can mess up and how
to handle those mess ups when you run
into them. But in my case, I got it the
first time. If you're working on this at
home while you're watching this video
and you didn't get it on the first try,
what you have to do is just interact
with the model to ask for changes and
adjustments as needed until you get it
right. And if it starts going off track,
you can just start over again or try
taking different pictures at different
angles and try again. You can also try
adjusting the prompt. All of these
things I'm going to show you as we walk
through the rest of this example
generating the listing image set for
this product. But the first primary
image we have already completed and is
done and ready to go. Okay. So, what I'm
going to do since I'm on a roll here is
I'm going to stay in the same chat and
just continue to ask for different types
of images. Now, here's where you start
to get into the interplay with the model
is that usually when you're generating
[music] product photography or product
imagery for Amazon listings with Nano
Banana Pro, you go so far in a chat and
then eventually it'll kind of go off the
rails and then you can try to course
correct or download the most recent
image and upload it into a new chat. So
you'll see examples of both of these,
but first we're going to stay in the
same chat and we're just going to say,
"Now create a lifestyle image of the
diffuser in a beautiful chic homey
living room." And I'm eating my fresh
blackberries while I talk to you guys.
By the way, hope you don't mind. This
will be like a mukbang style video. I
need the vitamin C. Okay, I'm sick.
Anyways, [music] this is the image that
we got back. Now, I can tell by looking
at this image that first of all, it
looks a little too perfect. Second of
all, the product is not the right scale.
It's too big. So, we're going to try
again. So, because the image doesn't
look too bad, but it's just it's clearly
not the right scale. Like, you can see
it compared to this coaster in these
books. And also, the image like scale in
general, there's like something a little
bit off about it. So, it's not bad, but
I wouldn't post it. So, what we're going
to do is a corrective prompt. I
literally just say, "Try again in a
different comfy aesthetic living room.
You made the diffuser look a little too
big. And here we go. It generated this,
which is really not too bad. The scale
is better. It's actually the scale is
not quite perfect, but it's very, very
close. And it's close enough that this
could be used as a lifestyle graphic.
Okay, so already we have one primary
image and one lifestyle image that we
can use on a listing. Let's keep going
and start generating different types of
listing [music] images using the model.
So, this next one, I'm going to try to
create a features graphic for [music]
the product. By the way, I'm in the same
chat here. And my prompt is now make a
graphic for the Amazon listing that
includes the benefits of the product. I
said benefits instead of features. Okay,
so I actually messed up in the prompt.
Make sure the product is featured in the
graphic. There should be labeled icons
pointing to each feature. So, I'm
confusing the model here cuz I actually
messed up. I said benefits and then I
said features. [music]
And then I list out the four features.
Ultrasonic diffusion, seven color mood
lighting, totally silent, and works with
any essential oils. And here's what it
gave me. Now, this is not great, right?
I would not use this on an Amazon
listing. Now, it's better than some
images I've seen on Amazon listings. A
lot of Amazon sellers use images that
are worse than this. In fact, I would
say quite a lot. Like, a big portion of
Amazon sellers use images that look
really bad and they're not mobile
optimized. So, the main issues with
this, first of all, it did get the text
right. Right. The icons are corny. The
design is weird. It used a moody image
of the product instead of like a nice
clean image and it's not mobile
optimized. So, there's a lot of problems
to it. So, first I'm going to try to
course correct in the same chat. So in
the ch same chat what I do is I try to
upload a reference image of another
competitor to show that I want it to be
like a clean features graphic not like a
cartoony one. So I upload this image of
a competitor's features graphic which
also is not great. Totally not mobile
optimized. Text is way too small. It's
not good. But funnily enough this is one
of the top competitors. And I say try
again. make it in the style of this
graphic from a competitor, but make the
text and icons bigger than it is on this
reference image. It should be optimized
for mobile. And here's what it gave me
back. Basically, the exact same thing.
And this will happen to you once in a
while. You kind of hit a wall with the
model and it's not getting any better.
And sometimes it'll just get worse and
worse. When you've hit that point, it's
time to start a new chat. And that's
exactly what I do here. So, because I
was hitting a wall, I abandoned this
chat altogether and I start a new chat.
The way to do that is with this little
square pencil icon in the upper right.
You just hit that icon. It starts a
brand new chat. And what I do is I
actually start over with the same
reference images that I originally
uploaded of me just holding the product
out of my phone shots zoomed in and
zoomed out on the product with my hand
and some other objects in the photo as
reference size references. and I just
say make a clean aesthetic features
graphic of this product to be used on an
Amazon listing. I have also uploaded a
reference image of a similar graphic by
a competitor but actually I realized
after doing this I didn't even upload
the reference image. I told it that I
did but I actually didn't. And here's
what it came out with. This is really
freaking good. We went from one that was
really bad to one that's mobile
optimized and really good. like this
image is great. Like if I paid a
designer and told them to make a
features graphic and then came back to
me with this, I'd be like, "Nice job.
You know, your salary was well earned
and we got this for free with this
model." Pretty amazing. Now, that's all
ready to post, but the only thing is I
don't like this lower left one that says
cool mist aroma therapy, cuz the whole
point of that feature is that it's ultra
quiet operation. And that's a really
important thing to customers of this
product is that it works completely
silently. So in the same chat, I just
say replace the text in the lower left
section from cool mist aromatherapy to
ultra quiet aromatherapy.
And then boom, it perfectly executes my
command. Changes the text to ultra quiet
aromatherapy. It looks great. This whole
image is ready to upload onto the Amazon
listing. And this is going to affect
Amazon listings conversion powerfully.
Now, I don't have to bring this into
Canva and do little edits. I don't have
to put it in Photoshop and edit the
text. None of it is gibberish. It all
came out great. Like, this image is
ready to go. And this is the first time
in human history that you can chat back
and forth with the model and get a
graphic like this that's actually ready
for prime time to upload straight onto
your e-commerce listings. It's pretty
cool. Honestly, it's not pretty cool.
It'sing game changer. One good thing
about this is that this happens with the
models. You kind of gain momentum. Like
now that we have a features graphic
that's good and has the vibe that we
want, we can piggyback off that to make
the benefits graphic. So now I say
create a similar graphic but for
benefits instead of features. That's the
only prompt I gave it. I didn't even
give it which benefits I wanted to
highlight. I didn't give it any context
whatsoever. I just said make a benefits
graphic and I let the AI figure out what
the benefits are and honestly it did a
good job. Like so we have long-lasting
quality about the materials. It says
durable stylish materials for extended
use. Then it says enhanced atmosphere
creates a relaxing and calming
environment. True. Improved wellness
promotes better sleep and stress relief.
Yes. Effortless relaxation simple
operation for instant peace of mind.
That's [music] a little bit of a mix
between a feature and a benefit. But I
mean, look at this. It got the little
tiny engravings on the buttons right. It
got the little hole with the light
right. It had it like lit [music] in
some pictures and unlit in others. And
it even got the different lit colors
right. Like this is an incredible
benefits graphic. And again, if I got
this from a designer, I'd be like, "Sary
well earned." You know, you did it. But
this I got from just chatting with a
couple minutes in a couple minutes from
an AI model which it just feels like
magic. So I'm sticking with this.
[music] But for you, for your product,
like I'm doing a speedun here for you
guys. For your product, you'll make
little tweaks. You know, you might not
trust the AI to come out with all the
benefits that are the most important for
you. Even though in this case, it
actually came out with some really good
ones. You might go back and forth with
it a little bit more. And that's fine.
It's still going to take you a fraction
of the time that it would have working
with a live photographer and a graphic
designer. So, it's all good. Okay. So,
the next type of graphic that I want to
create is an instructions graphic. So,
this is one of many different types of
images you can have on an Amazon
listing. There's actually about 22 of
them that you have an options for.
There's features graphic, benefits
graphic, instructionals graphic,
step-by-step, breakout, size scale
comparison, competitor comparison. I
have a whole list of them. What I'm
going to do is I'm going to give you
access to a fullon guide to Nano Banana
Pro that walks through the same example
we're walking through now. And in that
guide, I link to a full SOP on Amazon
listing image creation. So, you can go
in there and see all the different types
of images that you can create to give
you ideas while you're chatting back and
forth with Nano Banana Pro. So, I'm
linking that guide in this the
description of this video. It's the
first link in the description of this
video. Just click that and download the
guide. And then in that guide, you'll
have all the links you need and all the
prompts you need. It has a full prompt
library. Has everything you need to get
started with Nano Banana Pro as an
Amazon seller. So check that out in the
description of this video now if you
want to get some inspiration for while
you're doing this at home. Okay. So what
I'm going to do now is I'm going to
create an instructions graphic. So I
already have the four steps that I want
to be included in the instructions. I
want fill with water, add essential oils
of choice, press power button, and
select color to make it seem very
simple, right? [music] And this is a
very powerful way to increase
conversions of an Amazon listing is
using an instructions graphic. So all I
say is I'm in the same chat and I say,
"Now create a clean aesthetic
step-by-step instructions graphic to be
used on an Amazon listing. The
instructions should include the
following steps." and then I list them
out 1 2 3 4. So, here's what it came up
with. Now, at first glance, this
actually looks good. It's even got the
icons, right? It's got this little water
thing for the first step, fill with
water. It's got this little drip thing
for add essential oils. It's got this
little power icon for press power
button. Boom. It's got the switcher icon
for switching color. Like, and the
images are great. I the crazy thing that
really blew my mind about this is that I
didn't even show the model what this
product looks like on the inside because
I didn't open it up. It just figured it
out somehow. Like I think it just knew
from like this similar products like
this online and [music] like reference
those. Like I I don't know, dude. It It
honestly it blows my mind. [laughter]
It's really almost creepy. Like it knew
what was inside this product. I didn't
even show it open, but this is indeed
what it looks like. So, this looks good
until you look really close and you
realize that in these two images, the
ratios are actually different. Like,
this one looks tall and this one looks
wide. And that's when you're like, "Oh,
now people looking at this listing are
going to, you know, maybe some people
with an eye are going to know that it's
AI." It's kind of subtle, but it bothers
me. So, I wasn't ready to have this be
like my ready to upload image. Even
though I like the design, I like the
icons. It's mobile optimized, big text,
everything else is good. [music] It just
needs to fix this one issue of like
consistency.
Okay, so this time what we're going to
do is we're going to download this image
and we're just going to re-upload it to
another chat. And by the way, to
download an image you just tap the image
in chat. It opens up like a focus view
and then at the bottom you see this
little save icon. You just tap that save
icon and that downloads the image. So I
upload this same graphic into a new chat
and I say edit this image to make the
dimensions of the open diffuser in the
upper left and the one in the upper
right match exactly. And unfortunately
it didn't really understand my prompt.
It just gave me pretty much the exact
same image. This one still looks too
tall. This one looks wide. So, I try
again in the same chat before starting
all over, right? And I say, "Try again.
The upper left image shows the diffuser
looking too tall versus the wider one in
the upper right." And then boom,
finally, it understands and it fixes it.
And they look the same. They're not, if
you look really, really close, they're
still not perfectly the same height, but
it's so close that it's it's not worth
it. There's no one that would notice
that if you weren't looking like
ridiculously close. It just looks like
it's slightly further away or something.
[snorts] So, I'm happy with this. To me,
this is good to go. Ready to post. And
now we [music] have an instructional
graphic. So, we're getting there, right?
We're almost at the point where we have
a full Amazon listing image set ready to
upload onto Amazon. Let's get a few more
images and then we'll be ready to go.
So, the next type of image that I want
to create is called a competitor
comparison graphic. And what this does
is it shows us versus them. And this is
a very powerful way to increase
conversions on a listing. Sometimes just
this one image alone can significantly
increase conversions. So, what I'm going
to do is I'm going to upload the
rendered image that Nano Banana gave me
originally, and I'm going to give it the
prompt, create a clean competitor
comparison graphic to be used on an
Amazon listing for this product that
highlights the wood base, the nonBPA
material, the real ceramic body, the
soothing multiolor LED strip. I already
knew the four things that were most
important based on reviewing the reviews
of other competitors listings. So, I
knew exactly, you know, the the four
things that I wanted to compare that we
had that other competitors don't. This
is another point, by the way. Sometimes
you'll have specific things that you
want the AI to include. Sometimes you
won't, and you want to just see what
it'll come up with. Like when I did the
benefits graphic and I didn't even tell
it what benefits to include. I just let
it go for it and it actually did a
pretty good job. So, it's up to you. You
can get as specific or as general as you
want. And here's what I got back from
Amazon. Now, this isn't so bad. The bad
things about it are it's a little bit
overly designed. Like, there's too many
lines and stuff. It's not clean. It's
like too busy. And this Amazon product
comparison thing at the top is annoying.
But it did get the concept right, and it
got the words correct. Um, so it says
real stomach body versus plastic body,
genuine wood base versus faux wood, BPA
free versus plastic, a soothing
multiolor LED strip, basic or no LED
strip. So it actually did a pretty good
job. It's just the format and the design
that we don't really like, but in
general, the concept is right. So what I
do here is I simply say, try again more
simple, modern, and clean style. I
really like using these words with the
model when coming up with graphics
specifically for Amazon. modern and
clean style. It tends to produce pretty
good results with me in my experience.
And then I also say mobile optimized.
This is really important. I include this
in a lot of my prompts. And here's the
result. Our premium diffuser standard
competitor. And this is a completely
mobile optimized image. It's got the
check on one side, the X on the other.
This is a great image. Like this this is
a good one that would convert really
well. So again, we've got another good
image. We're almost there. All we're
going to do is we're going to add a
couple more lifestyle and inuse shots
and then we're going to have a full
listing image set ready to upload onto
our listing. So, what I do here is I
just again I went back to my original
photos of the product with my phone. And
I just say create a lifestyle image in a
comfy home with a millennial mom for
this product. This image is to be used
on an Amazon listing for the product.
And here's what I got. So, this is not
too bad, but it's weird kind of the way
she's holding it. And also, it's too
big. So, it keeps making it too big. And
I think the reason is because a lot of
the competitors versions of this product
are actually bigger. Like, the one that
I was holding is actually a small one.
So, when it's referencing images online
and on the internet, I think it's it's
learning from other sources that it it
thinks it might be bigger. So, it might
just also assume that my hand is
smaller. I don't know. So, in the same
chat, I say, "The product is too big.
Try again. Make it smaller. Determine
size by referencing the images I
uploaded." I'm kind of patronizing it at
this point. And then it gives me back
basically the same image with the same
scale. So, that didn't help at all. And
in this case, again, when you're going
nowhere in a chat, most of the time,
abandon the chat and just start again.
So, that's what I did. And I did almost
the same thing. I I uploaded the same
raw images and I said, "Make a lifestyle
image to be used on this Amazon
listing." I said, "His Amazon listing."
I That was a typo with a millennial mom
and a comfy home for this product. And
then I got this image. Now, this image
is actually good. The scale is right. It
doesn't look too big. It's the right
size. The only problem is it added this
eerie orange glow to the product, which
isn't actually there. That's not a
feature of the product. The only thing
that glows on this product is the strip
in the middle. So I say remove the
orange glow from the body of the
product. Only the thin line between the
ceramic and the wooden base actually
glows. And here it is. So it fixed the
image just from me prompting it. You
know that feedback. And this image is
good. It's the right scale. It's the
right setting. It's the right avatar
that's most likely to buy the product.
and it shows it being used in use. So th
this is a good lifestyle image. This is
a great lifestyle image that's ready to
upload on Amazon. Now we need one more
in the other most common use case for
[music] this product which is in the
office. So the two main use cases are in
the living room or a family room and in
an office. So we already have the living
room. We actually have two in the living
room, one with no person and one with
our customer avatar in it. [music] And
now we're going to do one in an office.
So, I upload the same raw images from my
phone and I say, "Create a lifestyle
image to be used in an Amazon listing of
a millennial mom using this diffuser in
her cozy home office." Because the
feeling I want to give for this product
is of cozy, comforting, because that's
the reason people buy [music] this
product to be comforted and relaxed. And
it gives me back this image. So, couple
things wrong with this image. one, she's
staring at it weirdly and caressing it
in a way that like makes like my butt
tingle in a in a bad way. And uh it has
this weird orange glow. Again, I don't
know why the model thinks this this
product like glows orange cuz it totally
doesn't. It's like solid ceramic like a
coffee cup. So, I don't know why it
keeps doing that. So, anyways, I try to
address the problem and I say she should
be focusing on her computer and not not
on the diffuser. don't have her touching
it. So, the thing is, when you have a
lot of problems in an image like we do,
the glow, the size, the creepy touch,
you don't want to try to fix them all at
once, it kind of confuses the model.
It's better to go step by step and fix
like one thing at a time. So, first I'm
fixing the um I'm just I'm like, "Hey,
have that chick like look at her work."
Like, she don't make it weird. She
shouldn't be like staring longingly at
it. Like that's that doesn't make any
sense. No one would do that. So I say
she should be focusing on her computer
and not on the diffuser. Don't have her
touching it. And it fixes it, right?
Puts her looking at the computer, which
again, dude, this is it's wild. It's
like being in the photo shoot and giving
the model directions and and she like
obeys you. Like, man, it's crazy, dude.
We're living in a crazy time. It really
It just blows my mind. I don't know what
life is going to look like 5 years from
now. like it's going to be trippy 10
years from now, 20 years from now.
Forget it. We're all going to be cyborgs
anyways. So, we fixed that issue. Now,
let's fix the next issue. And I say make
the diffuser a little bit smaller. Boom.
Does it now? I didn't even give specific
size requirements, but this is right. It
got the scale just right. That [music]
is the size of this product. So, now
we're good. The only thing left to solve
is the orange glow. And when I try to
solve this, something very weird
happens. And I'm going to show you guys
in a second. Very weird, kind of creepy.
And I almost saw like, whoa, is the AI
model like trying to send me like a like
a hidden signal or something? This is
how people get like AI derangement
syndrome, guys. Be careful. But uh yeah,
so I say remove the orange glow from the
body of the diffuser. The only glowing
part should be the line between the
wooden base and the ceramic top and also
the hole that the mist is coming from.
Those are the the glowing parts. And
here's what it gave me. Yeah. What is
that, my dude? Like, looks like
necromancy,
like a evil diffuser that diffuses like
poisonous gas or something. Pretty
gnarly. And definitely not what I was
going for. The funny thing is though, it
did add the glowing band here and it
added the glow coming out of the hole.
Like, it did a pretty good job doing
that. It just made the whole thing like
death ash black which is weird. So again
that creeped me out. I was like ah nah.
So I just downloaded the most recent
good image and re-uploaded it in a new
chat. You guys are probably seeing the
pattern now. And I just said remove the
orange glow from the body of the
diffuser. The only glowing part is I
said the same prompt that I said before.
And then boom. It gave me this perfect
image. Size is right. Product is being
used. The glowing part is right. So, we
got it all good. Uh, it's in the right
setting. We got the right avatar. This
is our last image. And we have now
officially completed the full Amazon
listing image set for this product. Even
though this video is longer than 10
minutes, this whole process
should only take about 10 minutes. And
like for me it took a little bit more
because I was documenting it and
screenshotting it along the way. But if
you think about the actual time to like
write in the prompts and then up
re-upload the image and stuff like that,
this whole process is about 10 minutes.
Now it might not always go that smooth
for you and it didn't even go that
smooth for me. I mean I hit a lot of
roadblocks like I mean you guys were
with me the whole time. Um, [music] but
I just got around them. And that's how
you have to that's like the creative
process of working with an AI image
generation model for your products. Um,
just like if you were in a photograph
photography session, a photo shoot they
called them, these kids these days,
you're directing the model and you're
getting different angles and you're
looking at the shots and then you're
making adjustments. You're doing that
but just in a chat on your phone and you
don't pay for it, which is pretty cool.
Now, if you're using the free version,
you're going to hit limits pretty quick.
The pro version is cheap, though. I
think it's like 19 or 20 bucks a month.
Uh, and then for they have like a
version for like big bigger companies
and agencies and stuff that's like 200
bucks a month, but you won't get
anywhere near those limits. I'm on the
20 a month plan for my personal uh
Gemini account, and I've never hit the
limits. So, you should be good to go.
Now, I created an entire book, a whole
guide on how to generate Amazon product
listing images that convert very highly
with NanoBanana Pro, and it actually
walks through this exact same example
that you went through in this video,
plus other examples like products with
labels and it has a prompt library as
well. So, it shows you like a starter
guide to the prompts that you want to
use for each of the [music] types of
images that you want to create and each
of the images that I created in this
video. And it also includes a link to
another SOP that shows you all the
different options for secondary images
and examples of high converting images
in each of those categories. And there's
we did benefits graphic, features
graphic, instructionals, competitor
comparison. That's only four. There's
actually like 22 different options. And
I have all of them listed out in the SOP
which is linked in this Nano Banana Pro
guide. So I recommend you guys check
that out. And if you want to get
inspiration while you're going through
this process yourself of different
images that provide a high click-through
rate and or a high conversion rate,
check out this video here. I'll see you
guys over there.